#### Contact

401 17th Street NW #3101 Atlanta, GA 30363 arcangyl@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/artboyatl (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

JavaScript jQuery Full-Stack Development

### Certifications

Learning Python

Unix for Mac OS X Users
Getting Started in User Experience
CompTIA A+ (220-1002): Cert Prep
8 Security and Organization
CompTIA A+ (220-1002) Cert Prep
7: Portable Computing

# **James Harris**

IT Digital Support Manager and Full Stack Web Developer Atlanta

## Summary

IT veteran with 20 years of experience in publishing, design, and technical support for newspapers and magazines. I have experience in multiple roles - graphic designer, software integrator and trainer, network admin, system admin, digital specialist, and web developer.

# Experience

Creative Loafing LLC IT Digital Support and Web Development April 2017 - March 2020 (3 years)

Greater Atlanta Area

- Reduced network expenses 95% by implementing a bid process for service providers.
- Scaled back systems by removing and repurposing outdated systems in addition to those no longer in production.
- Deployed a virtual private network and firewall security measures for both ethernet and WiFi networks.
- Migrated company email services to Google Workplace (formerly G Suite) from an Office 365 enterprise deployment by the previous owners.
- Moved the local IP phone system to a cloud-based telephony service that utilized the personal mobile devices of company employees. Sold the old IP phone system hardware to offset expenses for the cloud service subscription.
- Worked with vendors and with company personnel to facilitate purchases of personal computer equipment and new hardware.
- Deployed a NAS solution to house the company's photo archives from the last eighteen years

#### SouthComm

Network Administrator and Digital Support Specialist April 2012 - April 2017 (5 years 1 month)

Atlanta, Georgia

This was the previous owner of Creative Loafing Atlanta. I performed the same IT duties as with the previous owner, Creative Loafing Inc.

Creative Loafing Media
Macintosh Systems Administrator
May 2002 - March 2012 (9 years 11 months)
Atlanta, Georgia, United States

IT position maintaining all Apple systems for the entire company that included ad tracking systems, publication layout systems, as well as desktop, laptop and mobile hardware support.

Managing Editor Inc.
Integration Specialist and Site Manager
April 1998 - April 2002 (4 years 1 month)
Jenkintown, Pennsylvania, United States

- Project manager for the installation and training of specialized software packages for newspapers and magazines. Coordinated schedules with client site lead for hardware and software installation prior to onsite deployment.
- Managed an IPS Adtrac (formerly known as Roundhouse) installation team including server engineers and training personnel.
- Conducted installation projects for Gannett Newspaper, Les Editions
   Transcontinental (Montreal and Toronto), Newhouse Publishing, and Billboard (Viacom).

## Education

The University of Alabama in Huntsville

BA, Communication Graphics (Graphic Design) · (1984 - 1989)